falconsafety.com 2017-12-16

# Falcon Safety

### [Privacy Policy](http://www.falconsafety.com/privacy-policy)

**Binding Agreement.** Falcon Safety Products, Inc., (“Falcon Safety Products”) is providing this Privacy Policy to explain our data collection and use practices. By using or accessing this website or any of our other websites: dust-off.com, dustoffzone.com, falconsafety.com, shopfalcon.com, Falconsignalhorns.com, you agree to this privacy policy as in effect at the time of such access. (the “Sites”) IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY DO NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITES. You should carefully review this Privacy Policy

This policy may be updated from time to time without notice. Therefore, each time you access any of the Sites you should first review this policy and the terms and conditions of use before using or accessing any of the Sites. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes.

**Use of Site Limited to Individuals With a Minimum Age of 18.** The Sites should not be accessed or used by any individual that is less than eighteen years old. You represent and warrant that you are at least eighteen years old. We do not target any of the Sites to children less than thirteen or knowingly collect information from children for the purpose of selling products to any individuals under the age of eighteen.

**Communications From You.** Any communication or material you transmit to us by email or otherwise, including any data, questions, comments, or suggestions, will be treated as, non-confidential and nonproprietary. Except to the extent expressly stated otherwise in this Privacy Policy, anything you transmit or post may be used by us for any purpose, including but not limited to, reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication, broadcast and posting. Furthermore, you expressly agree that Falcon Safety Products is free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained in any communication you send to us without compensation and for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to, developing, manufacturing and marketing products and services using such information.

**Personally Identifiable Information.** When using any of the Sites, you may be asked to provide, or you may choose to provide us with or upload, certain personally identifiable information about yourself (“Personal Information”), including but not limited to, your name, email address, physical address and telephone number. In addition, if you make a purchase through any of the Sites, you will be required to provide information that is needed or helpful in connection with completing the transaction, including your name, shipping address, product selection and your payment information. We do not keep any credit card or other payment information longer than is necessary in order to comply with legal, tax and auditing requirements.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information.** Falcon Safety may also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as IP host address, pages viewed, browser type and other data, and may also aggregate any information collected in a manner which does not identify any individual (“Aggregate Information”).

**Use of Information And Opting Out of Distribution of Information** Falcon Safety may use the information you give to provide to you notices and information that Falcon Safety thinks you may find interesting or useful. You may choose to opt out of any such distributions by using the opt out mechanism that is provided or by sending by certified mail to Falcon Safety a written opt out election to the attention of WEBSITE Falcon Safety Products, Inc., 25 Imclone Way Branchburg, NJ 08876 We are not responsible for removing your personal information from the lists of any third party who has been provided your information in accordance with this policy, such as a business partner.

Falcon Safety Products may use aggregate Information for many purposes, including, without limitation, to improve and enhance the Sites, analyze trends, administer the Sites and for our market research activities. Falcon Safety Products may share Aggregate Information with unaffiliated third parties, such as business partners, manufacturers, distributors and retailers.

**External Distribution of Personally‑Identifiable Information.**

Falcon Safety does not externally distribute your personally-identifiable information, except if a user specifically opts-in that such user’s personally-identifiable information can be distributed to a third party. **[Discussion point]** External distribution does not include certain limited distributions such as sharing personally-identifiable information with a third party working on behalf of Falcon Safety, transfer of personally-identifiable information in connection with the sale of Falcon Safety’s assets or the merger of Falcon Safety or the disclosure of personally-identifiable information in connection with legal proceedings, investigations of crimes, or other governmental investigations. Transferring personally-identifiable information in connection with a sale or merger and sharing personally-identifiable information with an entity or person working on behalf of Falcon Safety is considered an Onward Transfer to third parties and will be handled as described below.

**Onward Transfer**

Falcon Safety shall only make Onward Transfers of personally-identifiable information provided by a user of this web site, in connection with a sale of assets of Falcon Safety or a merger involving Falcon Safety or the sharing of personally-identifiable information to a third party working on behalf of or providing services to Falcon Safety. Any such Onward Transfer shall be limited to third parties that (i) subscribe to the safe harbor principles of the U.S. Department of Commerce or are subject to the European Commission’s Directive on Data Protection, or (ii) have entered into a written agreement with Falcon Safety requiring that such third party provides at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by the safe harbor principles. ****

**Access, Review and Correction of Personally Identifiable Information.** You can by emailing Falcon Safety at [service@shopfalcon.com](mailto:service@shopfalcon.com) or call us at (800)-3FALCON to review and correct the personally identifiable information that has been collected from you by Falcon Safety.

**Use of Cookies:** Cookies are small files that are sent to your web browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Falcon Safety Products may use cookies to customize your visit to any Site and for other purposes to make your visit more convenient or to enable us to enhance our service. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or “delete cookies” from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use the Sites, but it may interfere with some of its functionality. Cookies will never be used to retrieve personal information from your computer for purposes that are unrelated to the Sites or your interaction with the Sites.

**Clickstream.** As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as “clickstream data”, can be collected and stored by a web site’s server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use and the address of the web site from which you linked to any of the Sites. Falcon Safety Products may collect and use clickstream data as a form of Aggregate Information to determine how much time visitors spend on each page of any Site, how visitors navigate throughout the Site and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors. This information will be used to improve our Sites and our services. Any collection or use of clickstream data will not intentionally contain any Personal Information.

**Security.** The security of your personally identifiable information is very important to us. Falcon Safety Products has put in place reasonable procedures to safeguard the information we collect. However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, it cannot be guaranteed that communications between you and us, or information stored on any Site or our servers, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers and your use of any Site demonstrates your assumption of this risk.

**Effective Date.** The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy is January 1, 2011
